<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media and Sports Journalism</title>
    <link>https://com267f17p4.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Social Media and Sports Journalism</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://com267f17p4.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter and Online Sports Reporting</title>
      <link>https://com267f17p4.github.io/post/quant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://com267f17p4.github.io/post/quant/</guid>
      <description>By looking at the content on major sports news outlets, we can get an aggregate understanding of how social media websites are integrated with sports journalism.
Twitter in particular has established itself as the social media platform most associated with breaking news. Journalists often use Twitter to take their followers behind the scenes or to give their personal views and insights. Though this use evolved and was established by the behavior of individual journalists, it now is practically impossible for many journalists today to work without some sort of Twitter presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media and ESPN</title>
      <link>https://com267f17p4.github.io/post/social-media-and-espn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://com267f17p4.github.io/post/social-media-and-espn/</guid>
      <description>On the topic of innovative cable news, many of us probably think of Ted Turner and CNN&amp;mdash;the first broadcast of its kind to offer 24-7 news in aggregate via network television. Although CNN first launched on June 1st 1980, they were not the first to implement this business model. In fact, ESPN beat them to the punch.
  Founded by Bill Rasmussen and his son Scott, ESPN first launched their American-based, global cable and satellite television channel on September 7th, 1979.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://com267f17p4.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://com267f17p4.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Carl Colglazier is an undergraduate student at North Carolina State University working toward degrees in computer science and communication.
Justin Capoccia studies communication with a concentration in public relations at North Carolina State University.
This website was created as a course project for Electronic Media Writing: Theory and Practice (COM267) instructed by Professor Justin Grandinetti.
Further Reading  Sheffer, Mary Lou, and Brad Schultz. &amp;ldquo;Paradigm shift or passing fad? Twitter and sports journalism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>